Guide to the George Ellery Hale Papers HaleGE
California Institute of Technology Archives and Special Collections
- Personal Correspondence and Papers Relating to Individuals, 1865–1950; 1; 20 linear feet (Tape HaleGE_01, Carton 1, Reel 1–40, Carton 3)
  - Edmund Beecher Wilson, 1909–1926; HaleGE_01_00_043_23; 18 pages (Box 43, Folder 23)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 37, frames 624 to 642.
  - Edwin Bidwell Wilson, 1913–1934; HaleGE_01_00_043_24; 355 pages (Box 43, Folder 24, Box 44, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 37, frames 643 to 999.
  - W. E. Wilson, 1904–1906; HaleGE_01_00_044_02; 29 pages (Box 44, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 38, frames 20 to 49.
  - Robert Woellner, 1933; HaleGE_01_00_044_03; 1 pages (Box 44, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 38, frames 50 to 51.
  - Max Wolf, 1932; HaleGE_01_00_044_04; 3 pages (Box 44, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 38, frames 52 to 55.
  - Dr. A. Wolfer, 1904; HaleGE_01_00_044_05; 8 pages (Box 44, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 38, frames 56 to 64.
  - Harry O. Wood, 1919–1920; HaleGE_01_00_044_06; 13 pages (Box 44, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 38, frames 65 to 78.
  - R. W. Wood, 1903–1935; HaleGE_01_00_044_07; 14 pages (Box 44, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 38, frames 79 to 93.
  - Casey O. Wood, 1931–1934; HaleGE_01_00_044_08; 22 pages (Box 44, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 38, frames 94 to 116.
  - Robert S. Woodward, 1903–1922; HaleGE_01_00_044_09; 2319 pages (Box 44, Folder 9-11, Box 45, Box 46, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 38, frames 117 to 1005; reel 39, frames 21 to 1362; and reel 40, frames 20 to 116.
  - S. M. Woodward, 1916; HaleGE_01_00_046_02; 9 pages (Box 46, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 40, frames 117 to 126.
  - A. W. Wright, 1910–1915; HaleGE_01_00_046_03; 20 pages (Box 46, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 40, frames 127 to 147.
  - Sir Almroth Wright, 1931–1932; HaleGE_01_00_046_04; 10 pages (Box 46, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 40, frames 148 to 158.
  - Fred E. Wright, 1927–1934; HaleGE_01_00_046_05; 65 pages (Box 46, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 40, frames 159 to 224.
  - W. H. Wright, 1905–1935; HaleGE_01_00_046_06; 31 pages (Box 46, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 40, frames 225 to 255.
  - Robert M. Yerkes, 1916–1922; HaleGE_01_00_046_07; 177 pages (Box 46, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 40, frames 256 to 433.
  - Yerkes Observatory, 1897–1905; HaleGE_01_00_046_08; 224 pages (Box 46, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 40, frames 434 to 659.
  - Anne S. Young, 1903–1905; HaleGE_01_00_046_09; 5 pages (Box 46, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 40, frames 660 to 665.
  - C. A. Young, 1897–1907; HaleGE_01_00_046_10; 47 pages (Box 46, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 40, frames 666 to 713.
  - P. Zeeman, 1910–1935; HaleGE_01_00_046_11; 29 pages (Box 46, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 40, frames 714 to 743.
- Correspondence and Records Relating to Organizations, 1863–1937; 2; 14 linear feet (Tape HaleGE_01)
  - International and Foreign Organizations, 1863–1937; 1; 3 linear feet (Carton 1, Reel 41–45, Carton 3)
    - International Research Council, 1917–1934; HaleGE_02_0A_047_01; 1168 pages (Box 47)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 41, frames 20 to 1181.
    - International Research Council reports, statutes, and miscellaneous documents, 1916–1931; undated; HaleGE_02_0A_048_01; 647 pages (Box 48)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 42, frames 20 to 664.
    - International Council of Scientific Unions, 1931–1937; HaleGE_02_0A_049_01; 548 pages (Box 49, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 42, frames 665 to 1214.
    - International Association of Academies, 1904–1917; HaleGE_02_0A_049_02; 41 pages (Box 49, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 43, frames 20 to 61.
    - Lists of members of scientific institutions, 1863–1927; HaleGE_02_0A_049_03; 122 pages (Box 49, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 43, frames 62 to 183.
    - National Research Council of Belgium, 1921; HaleGE_02_0A_049_04; 22 pages (Box 49, Folder 4)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 43, frames 184 to 206.
    - National Research Council of Canada, 1921; HaleGE_02_0A_049_05; 3 pages (Box 49, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 43, frames 207 to 210.
    - National Research Council of China, 1922; HaleGE_02_0A_049_06; 5 pages (Box 49, Folder 6)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 43, frames 211 to 216.
    - National Research Council of Italy, 1929; HaleGE_02_0A_049_07; 4 pages (Box 49, Folder 7)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 43, frames 217 to 221.
    - National Research Council of Japan, 1921; HaleGE_02_0A_049_08; 6 pages (Box 49, Folder 8)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 43, frames 222 to 228.
    - International Research Council of Japan, undated; HaleGE_02_0A_049_09; 14 pages (Box 49, Folder 9)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 43, frames 229 to 243.
    - International Astronomical Union, 1921–1937; HaleGE_02_0A_050_01; 201 pages (Box 50, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 43, frames 244 to 445.
    - International Astronomical Union Organization Meeting, 1919; HaleGE_02_0A_050_02; 152 pages (Box 50, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 43, frames 446 to 598.
    - International Astronomical Union American Section, 1919–1930; HaleGE_02_0A_050_03; 189 pages (Box 50, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 43, frames 599 to 788.
    - International Astronomical Union Committee on Calendar Reform, 1921–1922; HaleGE_02_0A_050_04; 4 pages (Box 50, Folder 4)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 43, frames 789 to 793.
    - International Astronomical Union Committee on Nebulae, 1922; HaleGE_02_0A_050_05; 13 pages (Box 50, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 43, frames 794 to 807.
    - International Astronomical Union Committee on Stellar Classification, undated; HaleGE_02_0A_050_06; 44 pages (Box 50, Folder 6)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 43, frames 808 to 852.
    - International Astronomical Union Committee on Stellar Photometry, undated; HaleGE_02_0A_050_07; 20 pages (Box 50, Folder 7)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 43, frames 853 to 873.
    - International Astronomical Union Committee of Solar Atmosphere, 1919–1925; HaleGE_02_0A_050_08; 165 pages (Box 50, Folder 8)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 43, frames 874 to 1040.
    - International Astronomical Union Committee on Telegrams, 1922; HaleGE_02_0A_050_09; 3 pages (Box 50, Folder 9)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 44, frames 20 to 23.
    - International Astronomical Union Committee on Time, 1922; HaleGE_02_0A_050_10; 11 pages (Box 50, Folder 10)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 44, frames 24 to 35.
    - International Union of Scientific Radio Telegraph, 1922; HaleGE_02_0A_050_11; 5 pages (Box 50, Folder 11)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 44, frames 36 to 41.
    - International Astronomical Union and International Research Council, 1918; HaleGE_02_0A_050_12; 199 pages (Box 50, Folder 12)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 44, frames 42 to 241.
    - An Analytic Index of Scientific Literature, undated; HaleGE_02_0A_051_01; 25 pages (Box 51, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 44, frames 242 to 267.
    - Committee on International Auxiliary Language, 1921–1923; HaleGE_02_0A_051_02; 53 pages (Box 51, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 44, frames 268 to 321.
    - Committee on Standard Wave-Lengths and Solar Spectrum Tables, 1920; HaleGE_02_0A_051_03; 7 pages (Box 51, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 44, frames 322 to 329.
    - Institute of Pacific Relations, 1928–1936; HaleGE_02_0A_051_04; 124 pages (Box 51, Folder 4)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 44, frames 330 to 454.
    - International Associations, 1920–1933; HaleGE_02_0A_051_05; 57 pages (Box 51, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 44, frames 455 to 512.
    - International Association of Seismology, 1920; HaleGE_02_0A_051_06; 4 pages (Box 51, Folder 6)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 44, frames 513 to 517.
    - International Biological Union, undated; HaleGE_02_0A_051_07; 9 pages (Box 51, Folder 7)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 44, frames 518 to 527.
    - International Critical Tables, 1923–1932; HaleGE_02_0A_051_08; 89 pages (Box 51, Folder 8)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 44, frames 528 to 617.
    - International Catalogue of Scientific Literature, 1920–1922; HaleGE_02_0A_051_09; 101 pages (Box 51, Folder 9)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 44, frames 618 to 719.
    - International Electrotechnical Commission, 1913; HaleGE_02_0A_051_10; 15 pages (Box 51, Folder 10)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 44, frames 720 to 735.
    - International Geodetic Association, 1918–1920; HaleGE_02_0A_051_11; 18 pages (Box 51, Folder 11)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 44, frames 736 to 754.
    - International Mathematical Union, 1920–1924; HaleGE_02_0A_051_12; 99 pages (Box 51, Folder 12)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 44, frames 755 to 855.
    - Institute of International Education, 1919–1928; HaleGE_02_0A_052_01; 21 pages (Box 52, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 45, frames 20 to 41.
    - International astronomical research miscellaneous memoranda, 1905–1908; undated; HaleGE_02_0A_052_02; 408 pages (Box 52, Folder 2–3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 45, frames 42 to 449.
    - International Institute of Agriculture, 1921–1934; HaleGE_02_0A_052_04; 247 pages (Box 52, Folder 4)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 45, frames 450 to 689.
    - International Union of Academies and American Council of Learned Societies, 1920; HaleGE_02_0A_052_05; 32 pages (Box 52, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 45, frames 690 to 728.
    - International Union of Geodesy and Geophysics, 1919–1929; HaleGE_02_0A_052_06; 291 pages (Box 52, Folder 6)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 45, frames 729 to 1020.
    - International Union of Pure and Applied Chemistry, 1919–1926; HaleGE_02_0A_052_07; 166 pages (Box 52, Folder 7)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 45, frames 1021 to 1186.
    - Industrial research, 1919; HaleGE_02_0A_052_08; 27 pages (Box 52, Folder 8)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 45, frames 1187 to 1214.
    - Inventions, 1917–1918; HaleGE_02_0A_052_09; 12 pages (Box 52, Folder 9)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 45, frames 1215 to 1228.
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1902–1937; 2; 2 linear feet (Carton 1, Reel 46–49, Carton 3)
    - Future, 1913–1915; HaleGE_02_0B_053_01; 292 pages (Box 53, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 46, frames 21 to 315.
    - Council, 1909–1930; HaleGE_02_0B_053_02; 808 pages (Box 53, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 46, frames 316 to 1124.
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1902–1934; HaleGE_02_0B_054_01; 296 pages (Box 54, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 47, frames 19 to 317.
    - Future plans of the National Research Council and National Academy of Sciences, 1924–1932; HaleGE_02_0B_054_02; 89 pages (Box 54, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 47, frames 318 to 407.
    - Site fund, 1919–1920; HaleGE_02_0B_054_03; 140 pages (Box 54, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 47, frames 408 to 548.
    - Building, 1920–1922; HaleGE_02_0B_054_04; 650 pages (Box 54, Folder 4)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 47, frames 549 to 1202.
    - Building, 1923–1926; HaleGE_02_0B_055_01; 319 pages (Box 55, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 48, frames 20 to 339.
    - Building dedication, 1924; HaleGE_02_0B_055_02; 127 pages (Box 55, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 48, frames 340 to 467.
    - Exhibits committee, 1921–1926; HaleGE_02_0B_055_03; 401 pages (Box 55, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 48, frames 468 to 873.
    - F. E. Wright and W. W. Campbell, 1923–1937; HaleGE_02_0B_056_01; 28 pages (Box 56, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 49, frames 20 to 48.
    - Mailing list, 1914–1933; HaleGE_02_0B_056_02; 624 pages (Box 56, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 49, frames 49 to 671.
    - Expansion of yearly elections to 15, 1914; HaleGE_02_0B_056_03; 86 pages (Box 56, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 49, frames 672 to 758.
    - Mailing list miscellaneous lists, 1914–1933; HaleGE_02_0B_056_04; .1 linear feet (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Foreign associates, 1920–1921; HaleGE_02_0B_056_05; 22 pages (Box 56, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 49, frames 759 to 781.
    - Medal awards, 1924–1925; HaleGE_02_0B_056_06; 10 pages (Box 56, Folder 6)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 49, frames 782 to 792.
    - Section on Astronomy, 1916–1937; HaleGE_02_0B_056_07; 63 pages (Box 56, Folder 7)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 49, frames 793 to 856.
    - Henry Draper Fund, 1909–1927; HaleGE_02_0B_057_01; 138 pages (Box 57, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 49, frames 857 to 994.
    - Nominations, 1914–1935; HaleGE_02_0B_057_02; 113 pages (Box 57, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 49, frames 995 to 1107.
    - Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, 1906–1934; HaleGE_02_0B_057_03; 305 pages (Box 57, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 49, frames 1108 to 1414.
  - National Research Council, 1903–1937; 3; National Research Council (U.S.); 3 linear feet (Carton 1, Reel 50–54, Carton 3)
    - General correspondence, 1916–1937; HaleGE_02_0C_058_01; 143 pages (Box 58, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 50, frames 21 to 166.
    - Miscellaneous documents and drafts of articles, 1916–1919; HaleGE_02_0C_058_02; 445 pages (Box 58, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 50, frames 167 to 611.
    - Reports of committees, 1917–1918; HaleGE_02_0C_058_03; 273 pages (Box 58, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 50, frames 612 to 885.
    - Publications, 1916–1923; HaleGE_02_0C_058_04; 260 pages (Box 58, Folder 4)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 50, frames 886 to 1146.
    - Research Council Bulletin, 1919; HaleGE_02_0C_058_05; 14 pages (Box 58, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 50, frames 1147 to 1162.
    - Army Ordnance, 1918; HaleGE_02_0C_059_01; 6 pages (Box 59, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 20 to 26.
    - Carnegie Corporation, 1918; HaleGE_02_0C_059_02; 85 pages (Box 59, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 27 to 109.
    - Council of National Defense Circular, 1916; HaleGE_02_0C_059_03; 2 pages (Box 59, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 110 to 112.
    - Committee on Supersound, 1919; HaleGE_02_0C_059_04; 17 pages (Box 59, Folder 4)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 113 to 130.
    - Executive Board, 1916–1920; HaleGE_02_0C_059_05; 45 pages (Box 59, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 131 to 176.
    - Engineering Foundation Board, 1916–1933; HaleGE_02_0C_059_06; 149 pages (Box 59, Folder 6)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 177 to 326.
    - General Munitions Board, 1917; HaleGE_02_0C_059_07; 4 pages (Box 59, Folder 7)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 327 to 331.
    - Government Division, 1919–1920; HaleGE_02_0C_059_08; 12 pages (Box 59, Folder 8)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 332 to 344.
    - Highways Research Project, 1921–1928; HaleGE_02_0C_059_09; 35 pages (Box 59, Folder 9)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 345 to 380.
    - Invitations, 1917–1919; HaleGE_02_0C_059_10; 41 pages (Box 59, Folder 10)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 381 to 422.
    - National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics, 1921; HaleGE_02_0C_059_11; 1 pages (Box 59, Folder 11)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 423 to 424.
    - National Research Fellowship Board, 1919–1937; HaleGE_02_0C_059_12; 353 pages (Box 59, Folder 12–13)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 425 to 778.
    - Naval Consulting Board, 1917–1918; HaleGE_02_0C_059_14; 7 pages (Box 59, Folder 14)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 779 to 786.
    - Secretary of the Navy, 1916–1918; HaleGE_02_0C_059_15; 12 pages (Box 59, Folder 15)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 787 to 799.
    - Navy League of the United States and Navy League of Pasadena, 1913–1919; HaleGE_02_0C_059_16; 34 pages (Box 59, Folder 16)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 800 to 834.
    - Newlands Bill, 1916; HaleGE_02_0C_059_17; 128 pages (Box 59, Folder 17)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 835 to 963.
    - Patent Committee, 1919–1921; HaleGE_02_0C_059_18; 191 pages (Box 59, Folder 18)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 964 to 1155.
    - Promotion of research in the United States, 1918–1920; HaleGE_02_0C_059_19; 13 pages (Box 59, Folder 19)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 1156 to 1169.
    - Research associates and council, 1903–1916; HaleGE_02_0C_059_20; 123 pages (Box 59, Folder 20)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 51, frames 1170 to 1293.
    - Research in the War Department, 1918; HaleGE_02_0C_060_01; 5 pages (Box 60, Folder 1)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 52, frames 20 to 25.
    - Research Information Service, 1918–1924; HaleGE_02_0C_060_02; 373 pages (Box 60, Folder 2)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 52, frames 26 to 399.
    - Research Institute of Physics and Chemistry, 1918–1920; HaleGE_02_0C_060_03; 130 pages (Box 60, Folder 3)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 52, frames 400 to 530.
    - Research Surveys, 1919; HaleGE_02_0C_060_04; .04 linear feet (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1919; HaleGE_02_0C_060_05; 3 pages (Box 60, Folder 5)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 52, frames 531 to 534.
    - Rockefeller Plan, 1918; HaleGE_02_0C_060_06; 16 pages (Box 60, Folder 6)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 52, frames 535 to 551.
    - Secretary of War, 1916–1918; HaleGE_02_0C_060_07; 51 pages (Box 60, Folder 7)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 52, frames 552 to 603.
    - Smith-Howard Bill, 1918; HaleGE_02_0C_060_08; 17 pages (Box 60, Folder 8)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 52, frames 604 to 621.
    - Woodrow Wilson, 1916–1930; HaleGE_02_0C_060_09; 85 pages (Box 60, Folder 9)
      This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 52, frames 622 to 708.